

Contacts

Phone: +48 531 310 527 E-mail: witold.a83@amail.com

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- · C+-
- InTouch
- Linux
- Python

Soft Skills

- Responsibility
- Ease of building relationships
- Ability to learn quickly
- Teamwork

DOWNLOAD CV





Witold Grzesiak

Engineer

I graduated from the University of Zielona Góra with a degree in Automation and Robotics, specializing in Industrial Automation. I am currently a Master's student in Computer Science at the University of Zielona Góra. I'm interested in new technologies and the application of AI in medicine.

Projects

- 1. Web Application Pokedex
- 2. Quiz Application JavaScript

Work Experience

Junior Remote Service Support Specialist at Ekoenergetyka - Service

August 2023 - December 2024

- Remote diagnosis of charging stations
- Remote repair of electric chargers
- Support for service partners, clients, and technicians
- Remote station updates

Junior Field Service Specialist

February 2023 - August 2023

- Repair of electric chargers
- Installation of charging stations
- Periodic maintenance checks
- Diagnostics of chargers

Service Assistant

July 2022 - February 2023

- Repair of electric chargers
- Installation of charging stations
- Periodic maintenance checks

Hospitality Leader at FMD Jadwiga Wieczorek McDonald's Restaurant

June 2019 - May 2020

- Providing guests with information about the restaurant's current offers
- Keeping the lobby clean and tidy
- Managing the cleaning team

Education

Computer Science, University of Zielona Góra

February 2023 – Present

Automation and Robotics, University of Zielona Góra

October 2019 – February 2023